HOW TO PLAY
SIRIUS
THE BUILD IS
THE FIRST GADGET
AND THE
second star power
BASICALLY
YOU HAVE TO
USE THE GADGET
TO SLOW THEM
AND
JUST 3-TAP THEM
The second star power
IS REALLY GOOD TO
ADD MORE SHADOWS
You don't have
TO USE THEM
every time
YOU HAVE
TO WATCH OUT
BECAUSE FOR EXAMPLE
INBRAWL BALL
IF YOU ARE LIKE
ONE-SHOT TO GET
SHADOW AND
SOMEONE IS SCORING
a goal
THAT BAR IS
GOING TO DISAPPEAR
SO YOU HAVE TO
WATCH OUT
FOR THE CLONES
you have
ALSO
WHEN YOU DIE
ALL YOUR SHADOWS
DISAPPEAR
MOST OF THE TIME
IT IS WORTH IT
JUST TO HAVE IT
ON YOURSELF
AND DON'T
USE THEM TO ATTACK
JUST TO
PROTECT YOURSELF
FROM BRAWLERS
LIKE MORTIS
I WOULD SAY
You can play
BASICALLY SIRIUS
EVERYWHERE
BECAUSE IT'S
SOOP RIGHT NOW
MAYBE NOT
INKNOCKOUT
BUTONMANY
OTHERMAPS
HE'S REALLY GOOD